xuqa.com 2009-05-01

# XuQa - Settings

Last Updated: 23rd December 2006 

XuQa.com is a free social networking & casual gaming website for young people, maintained by iVentster, Inc. as identified in the Terms of Use. For more information, please visit our blog ([http://huqa.blogspot.com](http://huqa.blogspot.com/))

Registration

When you sign-up on http://www.XuQa.com, you'll be shown two options. In the first option you enter your email, choose a password and create a XuQa login. A confirmation email is sent to your email address, which is used to verify your email address. The other option is to login to XuQa using a third party account (supported third party services are displayed on the XuQa registration page). 

You are required to select your college, school or city. You may also enter other personal information and any information you enter is optional and private, and accessible only to you or to those that you authorize.   
We are the sole owner of the information collected on http://www.XuQa.com. Personally identifiable information is collected from users at some points on our website. We collect the following personal information as part of the registration process:

\- Email address  
\- Name  
\- Age  
\- Location (city/country)  
\- Date of Birth  
\- Gender

You may also enter the following optional personally-identifiable information when filling in your profile:

\- Secondary email address  
\- Physical address  
\- Telephone number  
\- IM names  
\- School or College affiliations 

How is this Personal Information used?

Your registration information is used for the following purposes:

1\. To create your account.  
2\. Email: to identify you as a unique user, and to create a communications channel for notifying you of important service or security notices (required), or friend notifications (optional). When you sign-up, friend notifications are turned on by default, but they can be disabled by going to the “Settings” Page. Other newsletter or promotional emails are turned off by default.  
3\. Date of Birth: to verify that you are not an underage user.   
4\. Location: This is used to automatically place you in a group of people from your country.

Your Optional Personal Information is used for:

1\. Used by you to represent yourself to your friends.  
2\. In search results when users search for people with similar college or school affiliations.  
3\. Browsing photos: Your photos may be accessible to your friends or other users, depending on your privacy settings on the “Settings” Page.

Tell A Friend

When inviting friends to join the site you may enter their email addresses directly, or use one of our import options to import friend's lists. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. We do not store any of your friend's email addresses if they decline your invitation and do not join the site. We do not store any other information you provide to import friend's lists or invite friends. Such information is provided only and directly to the program or website you have selected to import your contacts from.   
As with any site that uses invitations and buddy lists, you should use care when disclosing your personal information to strangers. Be advised that if you send messages containing personal information, that information may be collected and used by others. 

Market Research Surveys 

If you choose to earn extra Peanuts by completing surveys offered by our research partners, the information you submit in completing this survey will be transmitted to them. However none of this information will be personally identifiable – it shall be used for research purposes only, and in aggregate form. You will know what the survey is about before you take it, and will have the option of canceling it at anytime before or during the survey. We do not work or associate with research companies that are in the business of trading personal information. 

Affiliate Offers

You can sign up for a promotional offer by an advertiser to earn Peanuts. This will require you to click on a link, and leave the XUQA site. Affiliate Offers typically require your name, age, location, and email address, though they may require more information. THIS INFORMATION IS TRANSMITTED TO THE ADVERTISER. ANY INFORMATION YOU ENTER ON ANY SITE AFTER LEAVING XUQA.COM BECOMES THE PROPERTY OF THE ADVERTISER, AND ITS USE IS GOVERNED BY THE ADVERTISERS’ PRIVACY POLICY. Before entering any information into an affiliate offer, you are advised to be aware of the advertisers’ privacy policies and their use of your information. 

Personally identifiable information

iVentster, Inc. is completely committed to protecting your personal information. We employ industry standard privacy procedures and security to protect your personal information, as outlined by this policy. We will not sell, transfer or exchange your personal information to third-parties for commercial or research purposes. 

We reserve the right to disclose information to enforce the Terms of Use of the Website, prevent fraud and misuse of the site, and to protect XuQa from liability or its users generally.   
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by United States law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

Choice/Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain notification purposes, when we ask for this information. If you no longer wish to receive your friend notifications and other communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each notification or communication.   
You will be notified when your personal information is requested by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.  

Kinds of Email Notifications

The following kinds of optional notifications may be sent to you by email, depending on your chosen preferences. These can all be changed by going to the “Settings” page on XUQA.

\- Friend Notification: When someone adds you as a friend  
\- Message Notification: When someone writes you a new message  
\- Photo Notification: When someone comments on one of your photos  
\- Crushlist: When someone adds you to their crushlist  
\- Actions: When someone sends you a new action

Please note that you may not opt-out of receiving important service or security updates.

Logging

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system and date/time stamp.   
We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected server data to personally identifiable information.   

Cookies & GIFS

A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. iVentster, Inc. uses cookies to keep you logged in to the site, and to enable the proper functioning of other services used by you on the site. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate within a few hours of use. We also use persistent cookies to identify users uniquely to reduce cheating and fraud. These cookies will stay on your computer even after you logout of XUQA. We do not use cookies to collect any non-XUQA-related information from any user. Most browsers are set to automatically accept cookies, however you can set your browser to prompt you or refuse cookies. This may cause problems in running and accessing some services on the website. 

We do not use “clear gifs” or other images to record, process, transfer, log or transmit any user information, with one exception: for security purposes, your email address is displayed as an image on your profile so that it cannot be “read” by a spam bot or automated program. Other than this security feature, we do not use images to process any user account or profile information. 

Third-Party Advertisers

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. Doing this allows the ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. We do not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or ad networks.   
This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by iVentster, Inc. and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

Survey Providers

Surveys may be provided to Users as a means to earn peanuts and other rewards on XuQa through our Survey partners, agents or affiliates. Surveys are completely optional, and you can elect to take a survey if you would like to obtain the supplemental membership benefits associated with it. 

Each survey is different, and will ask you for detailed information on your household, demographic, education, work, spending habits and other consumer areas. This information is not stored by XuQa.com, and is submitted directly to the partners, agents or affiliates we work with to administer these surveys. They use this information to determine which surveys are relevant to you and other users. Information that you enter into the survey itself will be submitted to the company(ies) who have commissioned the survey, and they will use this data in aggregate form for internal research purposes. PLEASE BE CAREFUL WHEN TAKING SURVEYS, AND ONLY SUBMIT INFORMATION THAT YOU ARE COMFORTABLE DISCLOSING TO THIRD-PARTIES OTHER THAN XUQA. PLEASE DO NOT DISCLOSE ANY CONTACT INFORMATION IN ANY SURVEY. 

When electing to take a survey, you will at some point be required to leave the Xuqa site to take the survey. While on another site, you are subject to that site’s privacy procedures as outlined in their privacy policy. Though we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other organizations and companies, we have worked to encourage Xuqa-affiliated survey providers to follow the privacy practices outlined in this policy. If you suspect there is a case of abuse, please contact us at [feedback@xuqa.com](mailto:feedback@xuqa.com)

YOU WILL NEVER BE REQUIRED TO GIVE YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS, NAME, CONTACT INFORMATION OR ANY OTHER PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION TO A SURVEY PROVIDER AFFILIATED WITH XUQA. If you have been asked for such information in a survey, please email us immediately at [feedback@xuqa.com](mailto:feedback@xuqa.com)

Data Center

Our servers are fully owned by us, but as is the case with almost all websites, our servers are located in an external server facility that is not owned, nor operated by us. Our servers and your information is protected by being in a locked data warehouse with highly restricted access, back-up power supplies, climate control and data recovery through scheduled back-ups.

The technicians and engineers operating the data center where our servers are located sometimes need to check connections for security and maintenance purposes. In such routine cases, they may look at your IP address and Internet Service Provider information to verify you as a real user (instead of a hacking program or a bot). They cannot access your Xuqa account and profile information that you have entered into the Website. This information about you is the same that is publicly available through your IP address to anyone you connect to via the internet, or any website that you visit on the Internet. 

Links to other sites

XuQa.com may contain links to other web sites (such as the “Our Blog” link at the bottom of XUQA pages). These other sites maintain their own policies regarding cookies and the collection and use of personal information. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

Your registration information is used for the following purposes:

1\. To create your account.  
2\. Email: to identify you as a unique user, and to create a communications channel for notifying you of important service or security notices (required), or friend notifications (optional). When you sign-up, friend notifications are turned on by default, but they can be disabled by going to the “Settings” Page. Other newsletter or promotional emails are turned off by default.  
3\. Date of Birth: to verify that you are not an underage user.   
4\. Location: This is used to automatically place you in a group of people from your country.

Your Optional Personal Information is used for:

1\. Used by you to represent yourself to your friends.  
2\. In search results when users search for people with similar college or school affiliations.  
3\. Browsing photos: Your photos may be accessible to your friends or other users, depending on your privacy settings on the “Settings” Page.

The security of your personal information is important to us. All XuQa.com accounts are password-protected. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

Warning & Disclaimers

Any information that you enter in publicly-accessible areas of the Website can be freely viewed by other people. These public areas include, but are not limited to, Blogs, Chatrooms, Poker Games, non-private Scraps, and picture comments. We urge you to be careful and sensible when posting in public areas – PLEASE DO NOT POST ANY INFORMATION THAT YOU DO NOT WISH TO DISCLOSE TO THE PUBLIC IN THESE AREAS. OTHERS MAY TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THIS INFORMATION AND CAN USE IT TO HARM YOU.   
We are not responsible for controlling the privacy or use of any information that is posted in public areas on the Website. 

Commitment to Children’s Privacy

Users under the age of 13 are not permitted to use our Website. Since we are committed to protecting children’s privacy, we believe that users under the age of 13 may not be suitable for participation in a public forum such as ours that is used by young adults. Online Services such as those provided by Hasbro, Disney and other children’s companies are much more controlled, restricted and heavily monitored, and more suitable for children and minors. If we are notified or become aware of an underage User, he/she will be removed from our Website. 

M&A

In the case of a merger and acquisition, or transfer of control of the Website or its parent company to another commercial entity, your user and account information will be transferred to the new owners or operators. This Privacy Policy will still remain binding and in force, and you will be given at least a 30 day notice if there is a substantial change in our Privacy procedures in connection with a sale or transfer of the Website or its parent company. 

Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

For any questions or concerns related to this privacy statement or XUQA, please contact us.  
XUQA.COM  
c/o iVentster Inc

114 Sansome Street, Suite 920  
San Francisco, CA 94104  
USA
